Don't worry. We shall find something to make you stand out
别担心 我一定有办法让你脱颖而出
Yona not want to stand out
约娜不想脱颖而出
Yona want to fit in
约娜想要融入
Quite
我懂
And by the time we're through,
等我们大功告成
it'll be like you've been going to pony dances your whole life
你就会像是天天逛舞会的小马一般
The more you know how things are done
去了解小马的风尚
The more confident you'll be
有助于你把自信立
There's more to a dance than just having fun
舞会不只是作乐的地方
And there's no better teacher than me
最好的老师就在这里
Rarity!
瑞瑞
Oh, Yona see!
噢 约娜懂嘞
When I'm finished to you
待我先让你改头换面
You'll start to fit right in
你会融入这里
Listen to me when I say
仔细听我的话语
Once you learn the pony way
学习小马的风习
You'll start to fit right in
你会融入这里
Right in!
这里
No need to wait another day
不需要继续等下去
To be part of our smart soiree
加入我们和睦的群体
The perfect dress, a color all the rage, but still unique
完美的礼服不仅鲜艳还要不拘泥
Now loose the braids, try a style more fantastique
解开发带 尝试更加时髦的创意
Here's what we'll do: A horn-icure and a de-frizz
然后来保养犄角 鬃毛深度护理
We'll dry shampoo this, whatever yak part this is
洗净香波 还有格格不入的怪异
Too curly, too blue
太卷曲 太蓝了
Too retro, too new
太复古 太新潮
Too Twilight, too furry
太暮暮 太多毛
We'll find one, don't you worry
别烦恼 定会找到
Choose what you want to be and be it
选好目标 不懈努力
Picture you to see and see it
看看镜中新的自己
I'm the mare to guarantee it
我不会辜负你
You'll fit right in
你会融入这里
My plan, my grand design
我的想法和设计
Your friends will thrill to find
让伙伴都称奇
A new you that's too divine
焕然一新的你
Yeah, you're gonna—
你一定会—
Yona gonna—
约娜定会—
Fit right in
融入这里
Right in
这里
Listen to me when I say
仔细听我的话语
Once you learn the pony way
学习小马的风习
You'll start to fit right in
I'll start to fit right in
你一定会融入这里
约娜定会融入这里
Right in
这里
Yak not waste another day
牦牛不会等下去
To be part of your pony way
融入小马和谐的群体
way
Yak not waste another day to
牦牛不会等下去 我要
Fit right in!
融入这里